Tracy Early papers, Inclusive: 1924-2005, Bulk: circa 1940-2005
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Subjects, 1924-2007; 3
  - Newspapers: Publication Attempts: Tracy Early: (8 of 8), 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Puerto Rico: Young Lords, 1969 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Puerto Rico: Young Lords, 1970 January (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Puerto Rico: Young Lords, 1970 February-June (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Puerto Rico: Young Lords, 1970 September-December (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Puerto Rico: Young Lords, 1971-1973 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Puerto Rico: Young Lords, undated (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Religious Right, 1983-1988 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Richard Nixon, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Richard Nixon, 1969-1970 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Richard Nixon, 1971-1973 April (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Richard Nixon, 1973 May (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Richard Nixon, 1973 June-October (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Richard Nixon, 1973 November-1974 April 4 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: Richard Nixon, 1974 April 30-July (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers: Richard Nixon, 1974 August-1981 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1968 June-November 15 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1968 November 17-18 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1968 November 20-December 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1968 December 1-6 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1969 May 1-10 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1969 May 11 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1969 May 21-30 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1969 July-November (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1969 December-1970 September (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1970 November-December (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1971 January-June (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1971 December-1973 May (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1973 December-1975 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1976-1978 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1979-1980 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1981-1983 May (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1983 December-1985 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1987-1989 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1990-1992 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1993-1995 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Riverside Church, 1999-2002, undated (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1969-1970 March (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1970 April-1971 October 8 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1971 October 15-30 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1971 November 3-7 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1971 November 10 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1971 November 24-December 19 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1971 December 29-1972 January 2 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1972 January 9-February 14 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1972 February 17-March 8 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1972 March 31 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1972 June-December (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1973 May (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi, 1973 June 15 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi: (1 of 2), 1973 June 16 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi: (2 of 2), 1973 June 16 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi: (1 of 2), undated (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Robert Browning: Casa Guidi: (2 of 2), undated (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1966-1969 October (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1969 December (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1970-1971 January (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1971 February (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1971 March 16 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1971 March 25 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1971 May (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1971 June-December (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1972 February-October (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1972 November (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, 1973-1989 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Roman Catholic Church: National Council of Churches, undated (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Ronald Reagan, 1980-1981 April (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Ronald Reagan, 1981 May-October 12 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Ronald Reagan, 1981 October 12-1982 January (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Ronald Reagan, 1982 February-June (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Ronald Reagan, 1982 August-1983 May (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: Ronald Reagan, 1983 October-1986 February (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Ronald Reagan, 1986 April-1988 February (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Ronald Reagan, 1988 April-December (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers: Ronald Reagan, 1989-1990 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers: San Antonio, 1972-1979 February 17 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: San Antonio, 1979 February 28-March 20 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: San Antonio, 1979 March 21 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: San Antonio, 1979 March 22 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: San Antonio, 1979 March 23 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: San Antonio, 1979 March 24-25 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: San Antonio, 1979 March 30 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: San Antonio, 1979 April 9 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: San Antonio, 1979 July-1984, undated (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Southern Baptists: Race, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Southern Baptists: Race, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Southern Baptists: Race, 1967-1968 March (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: Southern Baptists: Race, 1968 May-1969 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers: Southern Baptists: Race: (1 of 4), undated (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: Southern Baptists: Race: (2 of 4), undated (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers: Southern Baptists: Race: (3 of 4), undated (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers: Southern Baptists: Race: (4 of 4), undated (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers: Unification Church, 1977-1985 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers: United Nations: New York City, 1971 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers: Vatican, 1981-1999 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Continuity, 1966 March 9 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Continuity, 1966 March 13-1967 June (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Continuity, 1967 August-1968 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Hebrews, 1967 March 15-18 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Hebrews, 1967 March 31-April 1 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Hebrews: (1 of 2), 1968 June 29 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Hebrews: (2 of 2), 1968 June 29 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Hebrews, 1968 September 23 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Hebrews: (1 of 4), undated (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Hebrews: (2 of 4), undated (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Hebrews: (3 of 4), undated (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers: Wheeler Robinson: Hebrews: (4 of 4), undated (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers: William S. Coffin, Jr., 2006 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Committees and Associations: Presbyterian Lay Committee, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Committees and Associations: Presbyterian Lay Committee: (1 of 2), 1976 March 2 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Committees and Associations: Presbyterian Lay Committee: (2 of 2), 1976 March 2 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Committees and Associations: Presbyterian Lay Committee, 1976 March 9-May (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Committees and Associations: Protestants and Other Americans United for Separation of Church and State, 1950-1951 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Committees and Associations: Protestants and Other Americans United for Separation of Church and State, 1954-1955 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Committees and Associations: Protestants and Other Americans United for Separation of Church and State, 1956 January-June (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Committees and Associations: Protestants and Other Americans United for Separation of Church and State, 1956 October-1958 May (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Committees and Associations: Protestants and Other Americans United for Separation of Church and State, 1958 July-August, undated (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - Committees and Associations: Public Affairs Lecture Bureau, 1974-1975 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Committees and Associations: Rockford Institute Center on Religion and Society, 1985 November (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Committees and Associations: Rockford Institute Center on Religion and Society: (1 of 2), 1985 December 20 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Committees and Associations: Rockford Institute Center on Religion and Society: (2 of 2), 1985 December 20 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Committees and Associations: Southern Baptist Convention, 1967-1968 June 4 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Committees and Associations: Southern Baptist Convention, 1968 June 5-1969 June 9 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Committees and Associations: Southern Baptist Convention, 1969 June 9-1970 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Committees and Associations: Southern Baptist Convention, 1971-1999 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Committees and Associations: Sunday School Board: Southern Baptist Convention, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Committees and Associations: Sunday School Board: Southern Baptist Convention, 1968 March 13 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Committees and Associations: Sunday School Board: Southern Baptist Convention, 1968 March 25-1969 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Committees and Associations: Sunday School Board: Southern Baptist Convention, 1970 April (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Committees and Associations: Sunday School Board: Southern Baptist Convention, 1970 May (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Committees and Associations: Sunday School Board: Southern Baptist Convention, 1970 June (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Committees and Associations: The Society of Biblical Literature: Membership Directory, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 1965-1968 November (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 1968 December (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches: (1 of 2), 1969 January (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches: (2 of 2), 1969 January (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 1969 February-August (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 1969 September-1970 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 1972-1986 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 1989-1993 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 1994 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 1995-2000 May (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 2000 July-2001 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, 2002-2003 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, undated (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Committees and Associations: World Council of Churches, undated (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Sidebars: Correspondence, 1995-2000 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Sidebars: Correspondence, 2001-2006 April 23 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Sidebars: Correspondence, 2006 April 28-May 9 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Sidebars: Correspondence, 2006 May 20-September 5 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Sidebars: Correspondence, 2006 September 7-November 16 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Sidebars: Correspondence, 2006 November 16 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Sidebars: Correspondence, 2006 November 17-21 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Sidebars: Correspondence, 2006-2007, undated (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Sidebars: Correspondence, undated (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Sidebars: Data: PDF File, undated (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Sidebars: Grady Early: Notes: Diaries: (1 of 5), 2005 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Sidebars: Grady Early: Notes: Diaries: (2 of 5), 2005 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Sidebars: Grady Early: Notes: Diaries: (3 of 5), 2005 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Sidebars: Grady Early: Notes: Diaries: (4 of 5), 2005 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Sidebars: Grady Early: Notes: Diaries: (5 of 5), 2005 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Sidebars: Tracy Early: Memoirs: Originals: (1 of 4), 1983-2001 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Sidebars: Tracy Early: Memoirs: Originals: (2 of 4), 1983-2001 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Sidebars: Tracy Early: Memoirs: Originals: (3 of 4), 1983-2001 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Sidebars: Tracy Early: Memoirs: Originals: (4 of 4), 1983-2001 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Sidebars: Tracy Early: Memoirs: Transcriptions: (1 of 2), 1983-2001 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Sidebars: Tracy Early: Memoirs: Transcriptions: (1 of 2), 1983-2001 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1957 January-March (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1957 April-May (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1957 June-August 9 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1957 August 14 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1957 August 14-September 9 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1957 September 9-12 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1957 October-November (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1957 December 1 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1957 December 2-1958 March (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1958 April (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1958 May-June (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1958 July-August (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1958 September-October (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1958 November-1959 February 19 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1959 February 25-May (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1959 June-July 13 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1959 July 13-16 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1959 July 18-23 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1959 August-1960 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, 1971-1975, undated (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Correspondence, undated (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Pamphlet: Cooperation Without Compromise, 1970 July (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Pamphlet: United States Army Chaplain School, undated (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Churches: Army Chaplaincy: Photos, 1958, undated (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Churches: Columbus Avenue Baptist Church: Texas, 1951 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Churches: Columbus Avenue Baptist Church: Texas, 1952-1953 October 18 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Churches: Columbus Avenue Baptist Church: Texas, 1953 October 22-December (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Churches: Columbus Avenue Baptist Church: Texas, 1954 January-February (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Churches: Columbus Avenue Baptist Church: Texas, 1954 March-May (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Churches: Columbus Avenue Baptist Church: Texas, circa 1954 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Churches: Nyack First Presbyterian Church: New York, 1962 June-October 3 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - Churches: Nyack First Presbyterian Church: New York, 1962 October 30-November (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Churches: Nyack First Presbyterian Church: New York, 1962 December-1963, undated (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Churches: Rocky Point Community Church: New York, 1961 April-June 19 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Churches: Rocky Point Community Church: New York, 1961 June 25-September (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Churches: Rocky Point Community Church: New York, undated (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Churches: Roosevelt Memorial Presbyterian Church: New York, 1961-1962 January 16 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Churches: Roosevelt Memorial Presbyterian Church: New York, 1962 January 16-March (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Churches: Roosevelt Memorial Presbyterian Church: New York, 1962 April-July (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Churches: Roosevelt Memorial Presbyterian Church: New York, undated (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Churches: Rosemary Baptist Church: North Carolina, 1955 June-August (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Churches: Rosemary Baptist Church: North Carolina, 1955 November (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Churches: Rosemary Baptist Church: North Carolina, undated (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Churches: South Creek Baptist Church: General, 1956, undated (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Churches: South Creek Baptist Church: Photos, undated (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Churches: Supply Preaching, 1957-1960 July 25 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Churches: Supply Preaching, 1960 July 28-1962 August (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Churches: Supply Preaching, 1962 September-1963 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Churches: Supply Preaching, undated (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1953-1964 April (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1964 May-June 15 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1964 June 17-October 4 (Box 127, Folder 21)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1964 October 27-1965 January (Box 127, Folder 22)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1965 February-March (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1965 April-May (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1965 June-December 24 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1965 December 29-31 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1966 February-March (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1966 April-May (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1966 June-September 4 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1966 September 4 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1966 September 27 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1966 October 9-1967 September (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1967 October-1968 May (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1968 June-1969 July (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General, 1969 August-1978 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General: (1 of 4), undated (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General: (2 of 4), undated (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General: (3 of 4), undated (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: General: (4 of 4), undated (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Churches: Urbanna Baptist Church: Photos, undated (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Schools: Baylor University: Texas, 1952-1954 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Schools: Baylor University: Texas, 2003 October, undated (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Schools: Snyder School Districts: Texas, 1924 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Schools: Snyder School Districts: Texas, 1937-1941 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Schools: Snyder School Districts: Texas, 1942 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Schools: Snyder School Districts: Texas, 1943-1949 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Schools: Snyder School Districts: Texas, 1950-1997 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Schools: Snyder School Districts: Texas, 2000 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Schools: Snyder School Districts: Texas, undated (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Schools: Snyder School Districts: Texas: Photos, 1970-2000 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Schools: Snyder School Districts: Texas: Photos, undated (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Schools: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary: North Carolina, 1937-1956 April (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Schools: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary: North Carolina, 1956 May-September (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Schools: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary: North Carolina, 1956 October-1958 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Schools: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary: North Carolina, 1965-1991 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Schools: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary: North Carolina: (1 of 3), undated (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Schools: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary: North Carolina: (2 of 3), undated (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Schools: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary: North Carolina: (3 of 3), undated (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1956-1957 May (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1957 June-1958 September (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1958 October-1959 June (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1959 August-1960 March (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1960 July-1961 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1962-1963 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1967-1968 October (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1968 November-December (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1969 January-March 11 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1969 March 12-May 19 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1969 May 19 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1969 May 21-27 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1969 May 27 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1969 May 31-October (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1969 November-1987 (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General, 1988-2003 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General: (1 of 2), undated (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: General: (2 of 2), undated (Box 130, Folder 18)